Manager, Organizer, Logistics

Name: Sinisha Paspal



Date of Birth: 06.06.1977

Adress: N.Macedonia

Tel: +389 (0)70-207-275

e-mail: paspals@gmail.com

B-driving license

PROFILE

Graduated politicologist and manager for corporate organization, with 18-year working experience. 10-years in textile factories which work for European markets. Hard-working, communicative, self-motivating person, used to work with dead-lines and dedicated to the job. Active knowledge of the English and French languages. Also, fluent in communication in other Balkan languages(Greek, Ex-Yu,Bulgarian...)

In possession of certificates for languages and also for coding.

Coding with JavaSE and JavaEE; work with RDBMS-(MySQL,MS SQL Server);

Software engineering;

Web design (HTML,CSS,JavaScript, AJAX,jQuery,Bootstrap,Spring,XML)

Excellent know-how with WINDOWS tools. (Word, Excell, PowerPoint)

Owner of B-driving license, with experience of more than 200.000km through Balkan countries.

Work History

2004-2010, "TRIMOD - DOO" Textile company from Bitola. Employed as a manager of sales and organization of production, as well as organizer of HR. Also, if needed, lorry-driver and web-developer. The company's main markets are France and Spain, also small production for domestic market.

2010-2015 "TRIKOMOD – DOO" Textile knitwear company from Bitola. In charge for commercial planning, organization of production, sales, managing foreign markets.

2016-2018 "Big JAVA Void BJV Dooel"- Skopje. JAVA – programming for foreign markets. Software programming organizer, HR organizer, production, sales, commercial management.

2019-2021 "V.K.Soze"-DOOEL Bitola. JAVA and RDBMS enterprise, software development for foreign markets. Commercial management, Software engineering, HR organizer and Manager for other resources.

2022 "GreenStar DOO Bitola, Factory for gray-board production and other paper products (paper tubes, paper molds, etc.)"

Logistics department manager, Sales and Procurements manager and organizer, responsible for foreign markets.

2023 "Innaco-Prilep" F-ry for anatomic mattresses and pillows -organizer of procurements and sales

Education

1996 - High School - "Josip-Broz Tito", Bitola, N.Macedonia

2002- Faculty for Political Science-Belgrade, Serbia _politicology

2017 – 5.A.C- Business Academy Smilevski-Skopje, N. Macedonia , operational management in commercial structures

2003-2015 – certificates "INTEGRA-ULTRA" for JAVA-SE 1.8, JAVA-EE 1.8

MySQL,PostSQL,HTML,CSS,JavaScript,AJAX,jQuery,Bootstrap

2003- "ZAR-2" -certificate for French Language

2004- "TOEFEL-2" certificate for English Language